epfo.services 2018-10-30

# Disclaimer & Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. .

**  
****What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter

your or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase,

sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication,

surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

       **•**  To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

**How do we protect visitor information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We do not use an SSL certificate

       **•**  We do not need an SSL because:

**it’s** an informative **blog**

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard

drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s

systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity,

which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us

compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better

site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**

       **•**  Keep track of advertisements.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent,

or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer)

settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct

way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won’t affect the

users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services

will not function properly.

However, you can still place orders.

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website.

These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies.

We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

       **•**  Remarketing with Google AdSense

       **•**  Google Display Network Impression Reporting

       **•**  Demographics and Interests Reporting

       **•**  DoubleClick Platform Integration

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies

(such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or

other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions,

and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page.

Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative

opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s

Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control.

The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency,

enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services

must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the

United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the

development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the

Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is

critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via in site notification

       **•**  Within 1 business day

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals

have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and proce

ssors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals

have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to c

ourts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compli

ance by data processors.

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes re

requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from

being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

**To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

**  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can**

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Hyderabad

500013

AP

getluckybyme@gmail.com

Last Edited on 2014-12-08
